let quiz = [
    {
        question: "Who directed Lord Of The Rings?",
        option: [
            "Peter Jackson",
            "Steven Spielberg",
            "James Cameron",
            "Christopher Nolan",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "When was the Fellowship of the released?",
        option: [
            "2004",
            "2005",
            "2001",
            "2000",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Who race is Frodo Baggins?",
        option: [
            "Elve",
            "Dwarve",
            "Man",
            "Hobbit",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question:
            "How many Urikai marched to Helm's Deep in the Two Towers?",
        option: [
            "10000",
            "7000",
            "20000",
            "15000",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question:
            "Who was Frodo's best friend?",
        option: [
            "Merry",
            "Pippin",
            "Gandalf",
            "Sam",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "How many Oscars did the Trilogy win?",
        option: [
            "10",
            "17",
            "12",
            "20",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Who created the One Ring of Power?",
        option: [
            "Aragorn",
            "Galadriel",
            "Theoden",
            "Sauron",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question:
            "How many formed the Fellowship in the first movie?",
            option: [
                "9",
                "5",
                "7",
                "8",
            ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of Sauron's tower?",
        option: [
            "Orthanc",
            "Weathertop",
            "Bara-Dur",
            "The Prancy Pony",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Where do hobbits live?",
        option: [
            "The Shire",
            "Mirkwood",
            "Rivendall",
            "Moria",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
];
